(Dr Koothrappali:)But trust me,
you don't want it for a steady diet.
(Raj:)Now, you listen to me. I am no longer
a child and I will not be spoken to like one.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to go throw up.
- What's wrong with him?
PENNY: I don't know.
(Penny:)Maybe it's the local cuisine.
(Penny:)Okay, well, it's nice to meet you.
(Penny:)Just gonna set you on down over here.
And I'm gonna leave, so namaste.
(Penny:)And FYI, you'd be lucky
to have me as a daughter-in-law.
(Dr Koothrappali:)She's feisty.
(Dr Koothrappali:)I like that.
[SHUFFLING]
Raj, what are you doing?
(Penny(opening door to find Raj outside):)No, no notes.
If you have something to say to me, say it.
[IN HIGH-PITCHED VOICE]
Sorry.
(Penny:)Oh, sweetie, it's okay.